ringplus.net 2008-09-20

# LEXIS PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

( **Effective as of April 1, 2008** )

**1.                    ****Our Commitment to Privacy.** Ring Plus, Inc. (“us,” “we,” or “our”) has posted this notice to set forth our Privacy Policy. We designed our Privacy Policy to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other site you may be able to access from [www.RingPlus.net](http://www.ringplus.net/) (“Site”). ****

**2.                    ****Consent.** By visiting and using this Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, and you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of this Site is also governed by our Terms and Conditions of Use and Terms of Sale.

**3.                    ****Information Collected.**

(a)     Personal Information. We collect any information you enter on this Site, or that you give us in any other way such as your contact information. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.

(b)     Traffic Data. When you visit a website, you disclose certain anonymous information automatically, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit (“Traffic Data”). This Site, like many other sites, records this traffic data about users’ visits.

(c)     Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or to refuse to accept cookies. We may use cookies to store any of your personal information.

**4.                    ****Information Not Collected.** We do not collect your financial information relating to your payment for any on-line purchase. We do not receive, record, store, or control any such information. We shall not be liable in any way for the acts or omissions of the financial institution issuing your credit card, including, without limitation, their terms of use or privacy policies.

**5.                    ****Use of the Information.** We use the information collected for administering our business activities, and to personalize your experience on this Site. Occasionally we may use the information to notify you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers.  We may make any personal or individually identifiable information available to any third party without first receiving your permission, including when such disclosure is necessary for the following reasons: 

(i)                   To comply with a court order, 

(ii)                 To protect our rights or property, or 

(iii)                To enforce our Terms of Service.

**6.                    ****Customer Submissions.** We reserve the right, and you authorize us, to use and assign all information regarding your use of this Site and all information provided by you in any manner consistent with our Privacy Policy.  All customer communications, comments, feedback, information, suggestions, and materials (“Submissions”) submitted to us by you are not confidential and shall become and remain our property. We reserve the right to use any such Submissions. **  **By making Submissions to us, you hereby grant Ring Plus and its affiliates a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, worldwide, irrevocable, and sub-licensable right to use such Submissions without limitation or compensation. You make the following representations regarding your Submissions: they shall be lawful and fit for publication; you have made reasonable efforts to remove viruses or other destructive features before submission; you own the Submissions or have unlimited rights to provide them to us; you agree not to take action against us regarding any such Submissions; and you agree to indemnify us from third-party claims regarding any such Submissions.  We shall have no obligation to respond to Submissions.

**7.                    ****Protection of Your Information.**

(a)     [RingPlus.net](http://ringplus.net/) is an open social network.  By visiting and using [www.RingPlus.net](http://www.ringplus.net/), you are agreeing that you have no expectation of privacy, and that you are solely responsible for protecting your personal information.  You alone have the ability to control what information you enter.  You also have the sole ability to establish different access authority to different classes of friends and other users by utilizing RingPlus.net’s “Classification of Friends” function. 

(b)     Your access to some services and content may be password protected. If so, we advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone, and that you sign out of password-protected services at the end of your session.

**8.                    ****Children.** This Site does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18. We will never knowingly request any personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 18.  If we discover a child under the age of 18 has submitted personally identifiable information. 

**9.                    ****How You Can Access Your Information.** You can request access to all your personally identifiable information by sending an e-mail to [http://www.RingPlus.net/contactus.aspx](http://www.ringplus.net/contactus.aspx) .  

**10.                ****Changes to Privacy Policy.** If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change. We have posted the Effective Date, above, for your reference.  Your continued use of this Site after any posting of any changes will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

**11.                ****Questions.** You can always contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy by sending an e-mail at [http://www.RingPlus.net/contactus.aspx](http://www.ringplus.net/contactus.aspx).
